observation
наблюдение
hello-hello
здрасьте-здрасьте
in the blog and water I remember I have a
в блоге так и вода помню у меня есть
blog on youtube like a channel called
блог на youtube как канал называется
al-
аль-джазира у
jazeera I have an andrey navel and
меня андрей пупок и
somewhere I saw you nepal somewhere you
такой где-то я вас видел непал немде вы
seem to be drowning there for the war with ukraine
вроде там топите за войну с украиной
years
лет
I'm talking about the war more
я про войну больше
why  you call it why you call it
почему это вы называете ну почему это
8 you started talking rights and
называете 8 вы начали общаться права и
you need
надо
to study this post there is no electric
изучать этот пост нет электрического
just in general and beige asked why
просто вообще и бежевого спросил почему
you call it lags yes you are right
вы называете это лаги да вы правы valmet
valmet operation talk right
операция общайтесь правым
I will ask you then we will talk right
я вас спрошу то будем общаться правые
we need yes ok yes we will be with you  to talk
нужно да окей да будем с вами общаться
about military operations this is a war
про военные действия это война потому
because russia attacked ukraine so here
что россия напала на украину так и тут
breath stop stop before i asked you a question
вдох стоп стоп прежде я вам задал вопрос
when ukraine declared war on the russian
когда украина объявила войну российской
federation i don’t say that ukraine
федерации я не говорю что украина
declared war on the russian federation but
объявляла войну российской федерации а
why do you call it a war because
почему вы называете это войной потому
that is a war
что то война
give a definition  in and these you are the
дать определение в and эти вы
definition of war if you look like it’s
определение войны если выглядите что это
not a war, but we don’t have a constructive
не война а у нас так конструктивный
dialogue like that, I ask you a question
диалог не получится я вам задаю вопрос
in  by poll to the question you didn’t get from well
вопросом на вопрос не получил от хорошо
then let’s yamskaya you are on this the fighting
тогда давайте ямская вы на это боевые
of one state so against
действия одного государства так против
another state or political
другого государства или политических
groups if you can look there
групп если можете там смотреть с
using the armed forces to reach
использованием вооруженных сил дойти
now your definition of vine if you
теперь свое определение вайна если вы
think that on the other you don’t know exactly the
считаете что на другое это не точно
exact come on come on  on
знаете точное давай давай на
international law, this is the end of the world,
международном праве это прекращение мира
but tell me in which document it says this
а скажите в каком документе сказано вот
is the norm in the 3rd Hague Convention that
это норма в 3 гаагской конвенции что
war is the end of the world and what is
война это прекращение мира а что такое
peace in the
мир
sense of what is it you asked what
смысле что такое вот вы спросили что
is war and gotti war, then the end of the
такое война и готти война-то прекращение
world what is me tell me the definition
мира что такое меня скажите определение
with  this with this with this please their
с этим с этим с этим пожалуйста их
dictionary can, and that is, after all, war you
словарь может а то есть ведь и война вы
don’t send x3 legos of the mode you in the word
не отправляет x3 лэго режима вы в слово
war are defined through the word of the
война определяетесь через слово
end of the world and what does not define 3d
прекращения мира а что не определяет 3d
max like it and what is the world you cannot
max как она а что такое мир вы не можете
say and what is not  I can say
сказать а что такое не могу сказать
tell me that such a world wait did not
скажите что такой мир подождите не
crush what question what is peace
задавили какой вопрос что такое мир
war I answered you that according to  the third
война я вам ответила что согласно третье
gags to the convention war is the cessation
gags к конвенции война это прекращение
of something has died now of my very body my
что-то умер теперь моего очень теле моя
very clear it and you did not explain on the
очень это прояснить и вы не объяснили на
basis of what legal document you are
основании какого правового документа вы
talking about the fact that you have
говорите о том что у вас на территории
a war on the territory of ukraine and on the territory of
украины происходит война и на территори
which ukraine ukraine foreign ministry of ukraine
чего украина украины мид украины украины
ukraine  was up to 14, we can, which means you
украина была до 14 мы можем а значит вы
can go to the Ozhegov dictionary there, a
можете зайти в словарь ожегова там
dictionary of the Russian language of the Russian
словарь там российского языка русского
language there and see where the
языка и посмотреть где ставится ударение
stress is placed, the stress is placed on Ukraine, the
ударение ставится украина словарь
Ozhegov dictionary and gave were written dadash do not be
ожегова и дали были написаны дадаш не
sad, and now you can, and after
грусти и вот можете а после в одесском
that Ukraine appeared in Odessa from this year, you can
из этого года появилась украина можете
show me where to check that in Russian
мне показать где проверить что в русском
the word ukraine with an
языке слово украина с
emphasis on ukraine you can
ударением на украина вы можете
refer to turn to alexandr
обратитесь к обратиться к александру
sergeevich pushkin
сергеевичу пушкину
see haacha ukrainsk quiet ukrainian
смотрите хаача украинск тиха украинская
look now he is talking and how
смотрите сейчас он говорит и как павел
paul walks we are moving away from the topic is not so you should say murino there is a state of
должны говорить мурино есть государство
ukraine  you where nothing even should
украина вам где ничего не даже не должны
of come down and come down to earth
из спустись и спуститесь на землю
please, and who are you to give you nothing
пожалуйста а вы кто вам ничего не дать
, and while flying over you, I now asked you a
еще и летая над вами я сейчас вам задал
question, what is it to interfere with
вопрос а что такое мешать от него на
his answer on the basis of what
него ответ на основании какого
international legal document do you
международного правового документа вы
call what is happening in
называете то что происходит у вас на
Ukraine a war again in Ukraine there
украине войной еще раз на украине нету
is no such state  there is in ukraine if in
такое государство есть на украине если в
oil and battles ukraine say in ukraine
нефти и битвы украине сказать на украине
i’m listening to you i’m sura tell me and ask
я слушаю вас я суры вот скажите и задать
this very question but tell me in ukraine
этот самый вопрос но скажите на украине
i asked you this question i want to listen
я вам задал этот вопрос я хочу слушать
to it too the answer is nothing happens in ukraine
на него тоже ответ на украине ничего не
because ukraine doesn’t exist
происходит потому что украины нет такого
the states heard you are now
государства услышали вы сейчас
with him from the edge of your
находитесь с ним края со своей
statehood ask me about
государственности спросите меня про
Ukraine so then let's talk about coal
украину так тогда поговорим про углей
so what is the world to break this tragedy
так что такое мир вот эту трагедию
I won't break this
ломать я сейчас не буду в этот не
tragedy now I want to hear from you the answer to the
ломайте я хочу услышать от вас ответ на
question so that we ourselves can  which
вопрос для того чтобы мы сами на который
you are now looking at 7 ready to
вы сейчас смотрите 7 на готов еще раз
look again will burn out in Ukraine
смотрите выгорит у вас на украине
I say that we choose the state,
я говорю что государство выбираем
you understand that I live in the state of the
понимаете что я живу в государстве
UK  Raina, take this very
украина вот возьмите назовите этот самый
question, just the form of fly and on a crystal
вопрос как раз форму лети и на кристалле
from Ukraine and we will talk further,
от украины и мы с вами поговорим дальше
I would like to hear on the basis of what
я хотел бы услышать на основании какого
legal document
правового документа
you name what is happening
вы называете то что происходит у а
in our country, in which country of
стране у нас стране в какой стране
yours, what
вашей какой
Ukraine in Ukraine  you understand ukraine, well,
украине в украине ты понял украина ну а
I’m not the side of ukraine again, let’s
я не сторона украина еще раз давайте то
ask which country you are talking about which country ask about such as it is called
спрашивайте про такую как она называется
correctly to me such a wall ukraine i don’t
правильно мне такой стены украина я не
know which country ukraine can you
знаю какую страну украина может у вас
have some kind of republic there what is your
есть какая-то там республики какая у вас
weak position  give out and name my
слабая позиция выдавать и назовите мою
country it’s normal it’s going to be a nightmare
страну нормальное пойдет дастся кошмар
you understand when a person has a really
вы понимаете когда у человека реально
weak position he has no arguments and
слабой позиции у него нет аргументов и
he’s fine they don’t understand
он прекрасно они вообще не разбирается в
what he’s talking about at all so name my
том о чем говорит так назовите мою
country live my country correctly
страну живите мою страну правильно
show that you respect the limit you need to
покажите что вы уважаете нужно предел
say it simply  the horror of you should be a
говоришь это просто ужас вас должна быть
strong position, we should be
сильная позиция мы должны быть
prepared for dialogue, but in fact you
подготовлены к диалогу а по факту вы
don’t know anything, maybe  not
ничего и не знаете возможно ничего не
to know anything in order not to know and I don’t
знать для того чтобы не зная и не
need you to ask me a question
являюсь надо чтобы вы мне задали вопрос
about my country I won’t
про мою страну повторять не буду
repeat which of you about which country
повторите какую из ты про какую страну
without asking again I tell you until
не спрашивая еще раз вам говорю пока вы
you answer my question
не ответите на мой вопрос
our dialogue will not move further
наш диалог не продвинуться дальше не
I’m you asking me about
найдет я же вы спрашиваете меня про
some country about which I don’t know
какую-то страну про который я не знаю
Ukraine I don’t know such a country near the edge you
украина я не знаю такую страну у края вы
will answer my questions no I
будете отвечать на мои вопросы нет я сам
answered myself I don’t know such a country Ukraine
ответил я не знаю такой страны украины
if you ask me about Ukraine
если вы спросите меня про украину
ask about Ukraine on the basis  what
спросите про украину на основании какого
legal document
правового документа
do you call
вы называете
you talking about the fact that you have
вы говорить о том что у вас на
a war going on in the territory of ukraine no
территорию украины происходит войну нету
territory of the region does not know where such a
территорию края не знает где такая
territory of ukraine i don’t live ukraine
территория украины я не живу украине
we’ll do well so formulate with a
хорошо будем делать так сформулируйте с
normal name come
нормальным названием заходите ответить
answer my direct question wave your hand
на мой прямой вопрос помахайте ручкой
wave your head something  someday let me
помашите головой что-нибудь дайте мне
know if you're talking about
знать того если будете этом говорит о
how things are and the mechanics i'll
как дела и механики я просто пойду
just move on i have a choice go in just a dialogue  i
дальше мне выбор зайдите просто диалог я
would like environment fictitious country
хотел бы среда вымышленной страной
cavities ukraine if you can’t
cavities украина если вы не может мне
give me any constructive non-
дать никакого конструктива не
conformation then why should i communicate with you
конформации тогда зачем мне с вами
so i don’t understand except
общаться так я не поняла по кроме
invent answer my question i’m
выдумываем отвечайте на мой вопрос я
ready to answer just you ask my game
готов ответила просто вы спроси мою игру
i don’t know such a country press ask
я не знаю такой страны жать спросите
spend another country perhaps in
проводят другую страну возможно в
which I live ukraine is understandable and then
которой я живу украина понятно и тогда
we will talk
мы с вами поговорим
if you want to ask a question about ukraine
если хотите задать вопрос про украину
look the question again the question of men you
взгляд вопрос заново вопрос мужчин вы
asked me I need back the role of rhinestones
задавали мне нужно назад роль стразами
idiot you go no you must respect my
идиот вам идет нет вы должны уважать мою
country if you are already nothing and no one
страну если вы уже никому и ничего не
should and should not then yes, you are
должен и не должен тогда да вот вы
talking about the cult of Ukraine I don’t know
говорите про культа украины я не знаю
what Ukraine is
что такое украина
you understand me no
вы меня поняли нет
so that you still take it and
чтобы вы все-таки взяли и и себя
squeeze yourself out later play your desire
выдавили позднее играете твое желание
will satisfy another place
будет удовлетворять другом месте
ukraine true ukraine where such from
украина правда украина где такую из
ukraine during life  -some document where
украина при жизни какой-то документ где
Ukraine is written,
украина написано
maybe I agree with you
возможно я с вами соглашусь
international documents do not
международных документах не ставится
emphasize not well, on rights  silam of the Russian
ударение не ну по правилам русского
language
языка
somewhere where it is written ukraine is
где-то где написано украина
quiet ukrainian night pushkin if
тиха украинская ночь пушкин если уж у
he wrote with his grandmother pushkin there he could write
бабушки он писал пушкин там мог писать
there what you need older and
там что тебе надобно старче и
nothing you I want to hear the answer to
ничего вас я хочу услышать ответ на свой
my question for the same we now we are
вопрос для того же мы сейчас мне мы
not discussing it again now  look, you are
сейчас не обсуждаем еще раз смотрите вы
now discussing just a stupid whale,
сейчас обсуждаем просто кита
maybe yes, because what are
бестолковыми возможно да потому что вы
you talking about some
чё вы говорите про какую-то
non-existent I’ll touch urine your opinion
несуществующую тронусь urine ваше мнение
and how in hell you talked about some
и как в аду вы говорили про какую-то
non-existent labor how can I
несуществующую труда как я могу вам
answer you swepts don’t exist six
отвечать подмели не существуем шесть
vats to hear the answer to your  the question is,
чанов услышать ответ на свой вопрос вот
in order for you to hear the answer to your
для того чтобы вы услышали ответ на свой
question, you must put it correctly
вопрос вы должны его правильно поставить
if you put the state should not
если вы поставили государство не должно
yet, but I say it again, I don’t know such a
еще но я еще раз говорю я не знаю такого
sovereign, it begins the grave, I can
государ она начинается могила могу
tell you that he fought there from heaven to
рассказать что там сражался с небес на
earth if they lived then no one  I do
землю если бы жили то никто ничего ни на
n’t offend anything I choose I want to communicate
чем не обижу подбираете хочу общаться
such I communicated with nobody metal fought for
такие общался с никто металл сражался за
five times repeat so please
пять раз повторять поэтому пожалуйста
answer my question  grew up with anyone, the
ответьте на мой вопрос с любой дальше
status will go further, so the children, I do
пойдет статус так и дети я же я же вас
n’t keep you if you don’t want the kind of land,
не держу если не хотите вид земли добры
say the correct name of my country,
говорите правильное название страны моей
he’s such a cattle, this cattle should be
он таким [__] вот это [__] надо
put right in place, but they are
ставить сразу на место а вот они
specially Ukraine continuing to talk with them
специально украина продолжая с ними
about then Ukraine  ukraine is not
говорить о тогда украина украина это не
to respect their country if they want to
уважать свою страну если они хотят там
just say something there
просто что-то
let him tell you all he
говорят пусть говорит весь он тебя
should ask about your country let him
следует вопрос про твою страну пусть он
call it correctly ukraine so there is
называет ее правильно украина так нет
no ukraine so this is a
никакой украина так вот это
guy I am meat spectators in the morning so
парниша я утром мясные зрители так
specially there does what ukraine has  edge
специально там делает что украина у края
if we answer them not the question of
если мы будем отвечать на их не вопрос
this ukraine we admit then that our
этого украина мы признаём тогда что наше
state is some kind of ukraine if you don’t want
государство какой-то украина нет хочешь
to ask such a question, I’ll formulate it with the
задать такой вопрос задай сформулирую со
word ukraine
словом украина
and then only when you
и тогда только тогда когда ты
wave your
махнешь ся
bagnyuk at such a way we will continue the conversation with you
багнюк у такую так мы продолжим с тобой
then what  disrespect for our
разговор потом что неуважение к нашей
country is not a sign of this Russian
стране это не знак вот этого российского
fascism of imperialism such a Ukraine
фашизма империализма таком украина
outskirts of this Pushkin wrote outskirts 30
окраин этом пушкин писал окраин 30
Pushkin I want to pi  so he could write minutes
пушкин хочу писать он мог писать минут
for a poetic, let's say riff, then you can
для поэтической скажем рифы то можно
then use
потом использовать
what you need older in a fairy tale of a
что тебе надобно старче в сказке золотой
goldfish, this one is called and the flax case
рыбки вот этот звать и льный падеж был
was over there in the Ukrainian language in Kalinin
вот вон в украинском языке в калининском
remained Russian died dipped narrow
остался русском умер окунулся узкий
language deteriorated
испортился язык
under
под
and the dude specially specially Vitenko with
и чувак специально специально витенко с
disdain  speaks about Ukraine on
пренебрежением говорит об украине
purpose, this is done by the Ukrainian, you want the
специально это делает украинский хочешь
interlocutor to burn, and so on,
чтобы собеседник подгорел и так дальше
but he doesn’t want to run away in a whisper under the
но не убегать хочет шепоте под
interlocutor,
собеседник убежал
all these imperial propagandists ran away, so
эти все имперские пропагандисты так
they say that Ukraine does not
которые говорят что украины не
exist, this is the outskirts, and so on, so
существует это окраина и так дальше так
after the 11th fiction of Russia, they should all be
после 11 фикации россии должны быть
found and
найдены и
called up  to responsible from because
призваны к ответственны от потому что
it is they who find these like nightingales and
именно они вот эти найти как соловьев и
his brace burn this request and
скобе его сжигают вот эту просьбу и
hatred of the imperial doll not to all
ненависть имперскую кукле не и всем
other nations on federal channels,
остальным нациям на федеральные каналы а
but these ones are weird and
вот эти и чудит омил и
always create for their audience per
создают всегда для своей аудитории на
thousand people per 10,000 per 100,000  and
тысячу человек на 10000 на 100000 так и
books are supported by this background of hatred
книг поддерживает вот этот фон ненависти
for Ukraine hate  to the Ukrainian people
к украине ненависти к украинскому народу
and the
и
maximum client, but because they are being bombed and
максимум клиент а потому что их бомбит и
bombed from the fact that Ukraine is
бомбит от того что украина независимое
developing independent clay, they are sitting there in their
глина развивается они там сидят в своих
swamps
болотах
under imperial oppression and the serfs can
под гнетом имперским и холопы не могут
not say anything to their king
ничего сказать своему царю
and
и
subscribe to the channel put like petrova
подписуйтесь на канал ставьте лайк
we will stay in place
мы будем оставаться на местах